[Music]
K more course could this have been an
admission of guilt from Robert Durst is
Kill Them All an admission of
guilt I think so unless he's talking
about a great side of the laugh actor
I'm pretty sure he's confessing right I
mean what's his excuse It's not murder
it's
HBO
technically why do college athletes need
dollars okay they're getting paid in
education it's more like brain bucks
right that they can redeem at the
knowledge store to buy wisdom points and
those wisdom points will help them have
perspective when they are
homeless it's like we pay the players
that all good but really like I think
that that we're asking the wrong
question in a way and I I don't know
what that question is I'm a poop joke
guy hey America Larry Wilmore here if
you like the nightly show on Comedy
Central like us on Facebook too just
don't poke me I do not like being poked
you can Candy Crush me